That Little Shocker of "The Bad Seed" is Back to
Rock You in a Whole New Wonderful Way!
Kathy O' is a comedy, drama film directed by Jack Sher.
A movie publicist is assigned to keep the public from learning that
a beloved child star is an egotistical little brat.
Harry Johnson, played by Dan Duryea.
Celeste Saunders, played by Jan Sterling.
Kathy O'Rourke, played by Patty McCormack.
Helen Johnson, played by Mary Fickett.
Ben Melnick, played by Sam Levene.
Harriet Burton, played by Mary Jane Croft.
Kathy O' is a 1958 American CinemaScope comedy-drama film directed by Jack Sher and
starring Dan Duryea, Jan Sterling, Patty McCormack and Mary Fickett.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.